Mahan Asadi



Front-end developer

+98-9128476029
Mahan.asadiiii@gmail.com
Tehran
Mahan-asadi.netlify.app
https://www.linkedin.com/in/mahan-asadi-701690277

Profile

I have a year of experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React making me an enthusiastic Front-end Developer. Throughout my journey I have successfully completed over 30 mini projects that demonstrate my passion for web development.

In the five months I have been interning at MCI HUB and Pelle Innovation and Tech House. These internships have reinforced my love for React when working collaboratively with a team. I firmly believe that teamwork is the catalyst for innovation.

You can explore all of my projects on my website. I am genuinely excited about bringing my motivation and teamwork skills to a company.

Experience

MCI HUB, Shahid Beheshti University - Front-end junior Developer

May 2023 - Present

- I've learned the ropes of team collaboration and the vibrant startup culture, all while mastering popular React libraries and platforms.

Skills: Next.js, React.js, Typescript, Tailwind Css, Git.

Pelle Innovation & Tech House, Fatemi - Tehran - Front-end junior Developer

Jun 2023 - Present

- Collaborating with the design team to implement visually appealing user interfaces that improve the overall beauty of the website and user interaction.

Skills: React.js, Wordpress, Elementor.

Parvaresh Dadeha, Motahari - Tehran - Front-end intern

April 2023 - May 2023

- I've engaged with Angular as well, creating small projects to further develop my proficiency, while also working on data using SQL and the Power BI application.

Skills: Angular.js , SQL.

Projects

A selection of React projects:

- 1. https://online-english-school.netlify.app
- * TypeScript ReactRouter Tailwind GitHub Netlify
- I'm currently working on my project, diving into TypeScript for the first time. I've incorporated React Router for navigation, along with Tailwind CSS and iconsax-react. The project is live on Netlify.
- 2. https://setting-password.netlify.app
- * AntDesign ReactRouter Tailwind
- I really enjoyed working on a project that combined functionality and design. I
 used JSX to create it, incorporated Ant design, for password input and utilized
 React Router to handle tabs. The site offers both dark and light themes and is
 deployed on Netlify.
- 3. https://landing-page-via-react.netlify.app (Responsive)
- * Tailwind NPM package
- Getting started with Tailwind CSS was a little confusing, at first. I found a YouTube tutorial that cleared things up. In addition, I incorporated npm packages into the webpage introducing animations to elevate the user experience.
- https://expenses-manager-react.netlify.app
- ❖ JSX
- This project has provided me with insights into the relationships between parent and child components in React. It has shown me how React's features can be advantageous, in handling larger scale projects.
- 5. https://linkedin-analysing.netlify.app (Responsive)
- ❖ JSX Figma
- For the first time, I got into crafting a static website through Figma. I found it to be a really effective way for developers and UX/UI designers to team up and work together.

JavaScript and HTML / CSS Projects

- For a complete portfolio, please visit my personal website at Mahan-asadi.netlify.app.
- FlexBox Grid JavaScript ES6 HTML CSS

EDUCATION

Islamic Azad University Tehran North Branch - Software engineering, bachelor.

2015 - 2020

- Graduation Project: Explored 'Edge Computing for the Internet of Things' under the guidance of Mr. Jabe Dari.